#### **NICHELLE S. HAYES**

215 Tor Bryan Road Fort Washington, Maryland 20744 (240) 355-8980 Cell

Nichelle.s.hayes@gmail.com

### **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Sales advisor with 8 years of customer service experience and a part-time media and web technology student. Excellent oral and written communicator with the ability to research, collect data, conduct analysis, and report results. Exercise time management and efficient planning to execute tasks and complete projects. Experienced in troubleshooting mobile and home devices.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bishop McNamara High School Forestville, MD

Graduated Magna Cum Laude, May 2015

University of Maryland University College

Anticipated Graduation: Dec. 2020

- Major in Digital Media & Web Technology
- National Society of Collegiate Scholars

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

IT Support Professional Certificate *Google* 

April 2019 – August 2019

Responsive Web Design Certificate *freeCodeCamp* 

April 2019 – July 2019

## **RELEVANT COURSEWORK**

- Concepts & Applications of Information Technology
- Introduction to Interactive Design
- Fundamentals of Digital Media
- Principles of Web Design

# **WORK HISTORY**

Sales Advisor, H&M

June 2017 - Present

- Lead team in boosting loyalty membership enrollment, which increased converted purchases by 30% or more every week raising the estimated profit (sales goal)
- Managed a team of 8-10 people at a time
- Trained 7 employees
- Facilitated 25 department moves involving garment rotation, proper back-stock routines, and detailed garment care & presentation
- Constantly retaining knowledge of new products, sale goals, and campaigns

### Executive Administrator, CLRA Group, LLC.

August 2016-March 2017

- Managed clients, businesses and individuals, with saving money on insurance and benefits programs
- Made over 300 calls a day to book appointments with business owners to present product
- Designed a powerpoint presentation for business meeting with Kaiser Permanente
- Enroll clients in programs (Benefits Counselor)
- Facilitated with closing deals on open accounts
- Administrative & executive detail

### Social Media & Marketing Intern, CLRA Group, LLC.

May 2016-August 2016

- Created and edited 20 videos with fun, informative content about insurance and benefits for company's social media following
- Made over 300 calls a day to book appointments with business owners to present product

### Radio Host/DJ, WMBC Radio

September 2015-May 2016

- Hosted radio show "The Underground" every Friday night
- Operated soundboards
- Researched and provided outline of news & topics to discuss
- Set up playlists
- Communicated with listeners by phone and online queue

#### Sales Associate, Dunkin' Donuts Baskin Robbins

June 2012-August 2015

- Assisted customers with hundreds of orders, including bakery, beverage, and ice cream options
- Organized and counted inventory of over 300 items once a week; Recorded temperatures and proper
- Decorated 5 cakes for last-minute orders when baker was not present
- Custodial responsibilities
- Baked and frosted/decorated 20 dozen donuts for special orders
- Trained 10 employees

#### Website Designer, Mid-Atlantic Equity Ventures, LLC.

June 2011-August 2011

• Designed an interactive prototype company website using Weebly to create a safe space and provide resources for teens.

# **SPECIAL SKILLS**

Proficient in Office Suite products, including Excel, Powerpoint, and Word

Proficient in Adobe Suite Products & Creative Cloud including Photoshop, InDesign, Adobe Animate, and Illustrator

Proficient in HTML & CSS; Novice in Javascript & ActionScript

Proficient in operating MAC & PC Operating Systems (mobile and home devices)

Proficient in WordPress

Experience with Salesforce, Google Admin, & CRM